demco.com 2019-03-07

# Demco.com - Security and Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Demco, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the demco.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Demco, Inc.

* * *

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of this Policy.

* * *

## Changes to this privacy policy

Demco, Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the effective date at the top of this page.  We will notify you of material changes prior to their implementation by posting a notice on our Site or by sending you an electronic communication to your email address on file.  By accessing or using the Site after such changes are effective, you agree and consent to all such changes.

* * *

## Foreign Visitors

This Site is directed to persons located in the United States only, and is not intended for use by persons located in other jurisdictions. The Site servers are located in and are managed from the United States of America. Any personal information collected may be transferred and maintained in our records in the United States.  If you do not consent to this transfer, do not accept this Privacy Policy or otherwise use this Site.

* * *

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register on the Site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

* * *

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.

**_IP Addresses_**  
We may log and track IP addresses for systems administration purposes and for reporting usage trends.  Your IP address is usually associated with the physical place from which you enter the Internet, the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the browser software you use and your operating system, and the date and time you access the Site.  By collecting your IP address, we may record the page that linked you to this Site, the web pages you visit, the ads you see or click on, and other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform and settings you are using, and any search terms you enter on this Site.  IP addresses are not used to track an individual user’s session.  This information only helps us determine how often different areas of our Site are visited. 

We may combine certain information collected automatically (such as through IP addresses, cookies or click-stream monitoring) with any previously submitted personally identifiable information, including health information, that we may have received from you.

**_Geographic Location_**  
We may collect your geographic location based on your IP address and other location-based data.  However, we do not collect any device identifications. 

**_Analytics_** __  
We may use various third party internet vendors to collect, track and analyze track analytical data regarding Site usage and trends.

**_Web Beacons_**  
We use web beacons to help personalize your experience, similarly to how we use cookies.  We  use Web beacons to gather non-personally identifiable information about the number of users who visit this website, the areas which they spend their time visiting, and other demographic data.

**_Aggregated Information_**  
We may also aggregate information it collects by de-identifying personal information and combining it with other non-personally identifiable information to calculate and monitor the number and demographics of users of this Site.  We may use this aggregated and de-identified data to market this Site and may sell or otherwise use this aggregated information.

**_Web Browser Cookies_**  
Our Site may use both temporary and persistent "cookies" from us and third parties for analytical purposes to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

* * *

## How we use collected information

Demco, Inc. may use all Users’ information we collect for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To track analytical data and User preferences  
Temporary cookies are used to complete transactions with this Site and for other purposes such as navigating the Site, counting the number of visits to our certain web pages, and facilitating the ordering process. We also use cookies for remarketing, which may involve tracking cookies across multiple websites in order to serve you an ad on our behalf on other websites after you leave our Site. These temporary cookies are eliminated when Users exit their browser. A permanent cookie may also be stored on a User’s computer by the User’s browser. When the User logs in, this type of cookie tells us whether the User visited our Site before or if the User is a new visitor. The cookie doesn't extract any information from the User’s computer.
  * To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * To process payments  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except our payment processor, TrustCommerce.
  * To tell you about other products and services  
If you purchase items on this Site we may share your mailing address with our third party list broker and our sister-companies, in order to bring you offers from companies you may be interested in.  Should you not wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out of these communications when you make your purchase or at a later date if you wish to stop receiving these communications.
  * To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to opt-out from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

* * *

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Account and payment data exchanged between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.  Our Site has undergone testing by a neutral third-party auditor, TrustWave, which has rated our Site at Level C for PCI compliance.  All payment information is stored with our third party payment processor, TrustCommerce, and remains encrypted at all times.

* * *

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others, except our third party list broker and sister companies, as explained above. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

We may disclose User personal information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request. We also reserve the right to disclose personal information to protect the security of this Site, to protect ourselves and our affiliated companies against liability, and/or in connection with any sale, assignment, or other transfer of all or a part of our business.

**Opting Out of Online Advertising**  
To opt-out of remarketing advertising provided through Google, visit Google’s Ad Preferences Manager to customize your ad preferences and tell Google which internet-based ads you prefer to see.  You may also opt-out of our use of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.  If you do not want to receive those kinds of advertisements, look for the “Ad Choices” icon in the advertisements, which will contain a link to the privacy policy of the ad network that will provide you with information on how to opt-out of receiving such targeted advertising.

You can also visit the website [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to change your consumer preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain further information about third party ad networks and online behavioral advertising.

**Children's privacy**   
This website is not directed toward children under 13 years of age and we do not knowingly collect or use information from children under 13 through this Site.

* * *

## Do not track

We will automatically collect cookies and other non-personally identifying information when you visit this site.  Due to this automatic collection, we do not currently honor do not track requests.

* * *

## Third-party websites

This Site may link to, or be linked to, other websites not maintained by or related to us.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties or third-party websites, including any linked or linking websites.  To the extent that you disclose personally identifiable information to any such third parties, different rules may apply to their use and disclosure of personal information that you disclose to them.  We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such websites before disclosing your personal information to them.

* * *

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Demco, Inc.  
PO BOX 7488,  
Madison, WI 53707  
800.356.1200
